What can I do?
何してもいい?
It's okay to stand still.
立ちですじまんかもいい
Yes, it looks quite streaky.
そうだ ね、結構すじっぽいか
too.
も
Wow, I'm really horny today.
や ばい、本当に今日はムラムラする
Just now, just now, oh, that's disgusting.
さっき、さっきさ、 あー気持ち悪い
hey.
ね
I was so horny because it was my size.
う ちらサイズだからムラムラしてたの
I don't do that anymore these days.
そうしたの、最近はもうしてないよ
Okay, let's make it a little lukewarm.
よ いしょ、ちょっとぬるぐりにしよう
It's going to get cold.
冷たくなっちゃうさ
Horny.
ムラムチ
You've been looking at me for a while now, haven't you?
さっきからちょっとしみてるでしょ
I was able to steal the pee.
おしっこを奪えたの
It's painful.
しみてるよ
Let's make it stronger.
もっと強くしちゃおう
Smell Minami's dog.
みなみのワンコの匂い嗅いで
The room smells like urine.
部屋の中おしっこ臭い
Take out your tongue.
ベロ出して
Minami, I want Oku-chan.
みなみ、おくちゃん欲しいよ
Pee, it's soaked.
おしっこね、びしょびしょ
I like it because I'm watching you pee.
お しっこみてるから好きだよ
It smells like urine.
すっごいおしっこ臭い
Ah, it smells bad.
あー臭くなっちゃった
What will happen if I don't pull this out?
これ引かないとやばいくんどうなっちゃう
Okay, let's drink some water.
よいしょ、ちょっとお水飲む
Please kneel.
膝立ちお願い
Is this what suji means?
スジってこういうこと?
Does it match?
合っている?
Now.
だいま
I want to have anal.
アナルしたいな
Can I have anal?
アナルしてもいい?
I want to spread it out with streaks.
スジで広げてみたい
It's like a mouth.
口みたい
The mouth looks like this.
口はこんな感じ
thank you.
ありがとう
In the back.
バックで
Okay.
よ いしょ
Furifuri.
ふりふり
This is what anal looks like.
アナルはこんな感じだよ
cormorant
う
Hehe hehe.
ふふ ふ
Good.
よいしょ
I made a mistake.
間違えた
Okay, then.
よし、じゃあ
Should I have anal?
アナルしちゃおうかな
Can I have anal?
アナルしてもいい?
I can't stand it.
我慢できないで
Then I'll do anal.
じゃあアナルするね
Good.
よいしょ
I need this girl when I have anal.
アナルするときはこの子がないと
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Lift your hips.
腰を浮かせて
Oh, it feels so good.
あーやばい気持ちいい
I wasn't wearing lotion.
ローションつけてなかった
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
I have lotion on.
ローションついてる
Good.
よいしょ
Okay.
よ いしょ
Oh, that's terrible.
あーやばい
I'm going in, I'm going in.
入っちゃう入っちゃう
amazing.
すごい
Good.
よいしょ
Let's lower it a little.
ちょっと下げよう
Anal is amazing.
アナルすごー
Se
セ
I've had sex before.
ック スしたことあるよ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I can put this much in.
こんなに入れちゃうよ
It's amazingly tight in the anus.
アナルですごい締められる
I like getting fucked with my anus inserted.
アナル入れたままくり当てるの好き
Feels good.
気持ちいい